# Rebecca King

#### CONTACT

2165700627 rebecca.lynne.king@gmail.com 6309 Ellen Ave. Cleveland, OH 44102

## **SKILLS**

JavaScript
HTML
CSS
CSS Preprocessors (i.e. Less)
Git version control
jQuery
Progress OpenEdge
WordPress
PHP
React

#### **EDUCATION**

General Assembly
Software Engineering
Immersive, project-based program
in full stack web development.
Independent and collaborative
learning in JavaScript, jQuery,
React, Angular, SQL, MongoDB,
HTML, CSS, PHP, and Git version
control.

Miami University
Bachelor of Science
Kinesiology and Environmental
Science
Graduated with honors.
Member, Miami University
Choraliers.

#### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I am a full stack web developer with front end expertise, and I am passionate about creating accessible online experiences for diverse populations. I believe that responsive design is key to creating a more usable Internet, and I work closely with design professionals and informational technologists to bring their visions to life. Portfolio at rebeccaking.info.

# **EXPERIENCE**

# Amerimark Direct, LLC, Web Developer

Middleburg Heights, OH - Nov 2020 - Current

- Developed front and back end solutions based on design specifications and information technology needs, working alongside diverse teams towards common goals.
- Researched and implemented practical solutions to accessibility problems on our sites.
- Primary front-end specialist on a team of web developers.
- Completed training in React and web accessibility.

#### North Coast Media, Web Developer

CLEVELAND, OH - Jan 2020 - Jul 2020

- Full stack development of websites based on a WordPress CMS.
- Technologies used include HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Git, WordPress, PHP, SQL, Google Tag Manager.
- Developed websites to work properly across multiple browsers, including those created by Microsoft, Google, and Mozilla.

## Ohio University, Graduate Assistant

Athens, OH - Aug 2017 - May 2019

- Created and maintained digital media platforms, including Wordpress.com websites.
- Learned about the principles of online journalism as they apply to the fields of medicine and environmental science.

# Americorps - La Puente Shelter, Community Educator and Volunteer Coordinator

Alamosa, CO - Aug 2016 - Jan 2017

- Developed, prepared, and presented program information to guide awareness, share findings, and build community relationships.
- Introduced to Adobe Photoshop and Indesign through training with a professional graphic designer.